<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Categories on SOTTOVUOTO</title>
    <link>https://sottovuoto.github.io/me/categories/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Categories on SOTTOVUOTO</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://sottovuoto.github.io/me/categories/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Hugo</title>
      <link>https://sottovuoto.github.io/me/hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 17:52:40 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sottovuoto.github.io/me/hugo/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h4 id=&#34;so-this-website-is-also-my-first-experiment-with-hugo--github-pages-and-one-of-my-very-few-experiments-with-developing-overall&#34;&gt;So this website is also my first experiment with Hugo + Github pages. And one of my very few experiments with developing overall.&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I know. Lame. But what else would you expect from someon that has never touched the code, if not for a couple of lessons at school? This website is only a place where I can park some thoughts and I wanted something simple and minimalistic, easy to deploy. I&amp;rsquo;ve read some suggestions online and I landed into this solution that involves Hugo as a static website generator and Github Pages as a hosting place. Ah, forgot to mention, I also wanted something to be free, so I don&amp;rsquo;t incur in the problem to have billings out of control. This solution satisfied me, in the end.
The only flip-side is that, with this method, you have to generate a new website each time you deploy a new edit or post. This is not the most efficient way to update the website, but maybe I&amp;rsquo;m just unfamiliar with it.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>First day</title>
      <link>https://sottovuoto.github.io/me/first-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 00:57:41 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sottovuoto.github.io/me/first-day/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;So here we are. It&amp;rsquo;s been a while, uh?
This is my first attempt to create an independent little website where I will talk about everything and whatever, so stick around.
Mostly I will talk about art, design, food, popular culture and the occasional rant.
I come from Mastodon, so you had probably met me already there. If not, I&amp;rsquo;m CONTESTO, go follow me! @contesto@mastodon.uno&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Beside that, a little about me:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;My name is Lorenzo&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I am 29 y.o.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I was born in Trento [IT]&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I studied graphic design &amp;amp; communication&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I just started a little community about Japan on Feddit here: &lt;a href=&#34;https://feddit.it/c/giappone&#34;&gt;https://feddit.it/c/giappone&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If you like Weval, we can be good friends&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
